<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Satire on FM-Lead</title>
    <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Satire on FM-Lead</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>© 2026 </copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>asset code on staff</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/asset-code-on-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/asset-code-on-staff/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Free Muser - Satire&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>audit</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/audit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/audit/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Free Muser - Satire&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Before using kettle, staff need RAMS</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-kettle-ptw-rams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-kettle-ptw-rams/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before Using the Office Kettle, Staff Must Complete RAMS&#xA;There was a time — a simpler, more innocent era — when making tea at work involved:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Walking to the pantry&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Turning on the kettle&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Drinking tea&#xA;But that was before HSE discovered the kettle is basically a boiling, steaming, electrically charged death machine waiting to unleash chaos.&#xA;Now?&#xA;Before you even look at the kettle, you must complete:&#xA;RAMS — Risk Assessment &amp;amp; Method Statement&#xA;Because nothing says “competent adult” like needing a 12 page document to boil water.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The New HSE Truth: Kettles Are Lethal Weapons&#xA;According to modern safety doctrine, kettles are responsible for:&#xA;•&#x9;Burns&#xA;•&#x9;Scalds&#xA;•&#x9;Steam injuries&#xA;•&#x9;Electrical hazards&#xA;•&#x9;Slips&#xA;•&#x9;Trips&#xA;•&#x9;Falls&#xA;•&#x9;Emotional trauma&#xA;•&#x9;Existential dread&#xA;•&#x9;And the possibility — however remote — of someone getting slightly wet&#xA;Therefore, kettles must be treated with the same seriousness as:&#xA;•&#x9;High voltage switchgear&#xA;•&#x9;Confined space entry&#xA;•&#x9;Nuclear reactors&#xA;•&#x9;Summoning demons&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bigger your title, the bigger your forehead sticker should be.</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/bigger-title-bigger-forehead-tattoo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/bigger-title-bigger-forehead-tattoo/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Bigger Your Job Title, the Bigger Your Forehead Sticker Should Be&#xA;Corporate hierarchy used to be simple:&#xA;•&#x9;Junior staff did the work&#xA;•&#x9;Managers took the credit&#xA;•&#x9;Directors took the blame&#xA;•&#x9;VPs took the bonuses&#xA;But in today’s Facilities and CRES world, titles have evolved into status symbols, and status symbols must be visible.&#xA;Which is why I propose the only fair, transparent, scientifically correct system:&#xA;The bigger your title, the bigger your forehead sticker should be.&#xA;Because nothing says “leadership” like a giant fluorescent label slapped across your skull.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Employees who work on any floor above ground floor are effectively working at heights</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-work-at-height-desk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-work-at-height-desk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Employees Working on Any Floor Above Ground Floor Are Officially “Working at Heights”&#xA;Once upon a time, “working at heights” meant something simple:&#xA;•&#x9;Climbing a ladder&#xA;•&#x9;Standing on scaffolding&#xA;•&#x9;Hanging off the side of a building like a Spider Man intern&#xA;But that was before HSE discovered a terrifying truth:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Anything above ground level is technically a height.&#xA;Therefore, everyone is always working at heights.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;Congratulations.&#xA;If you work on the 1st floor, you’re basically a stunt performer now.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From routine maintenance to 24/7 continuous maintenance</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/maximum-maintenance-24-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/maximum-maintenance-24-7/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Routine Maintenance Is Dead. Long Live 24/7 Continuous Maintenance.&#xA;Some industries believe in “routine maintenance.”&#xA;A schedule.&#xA;A plan.&#xA;A calm, rational approach to asset care.&#xA;But in Facilities and CRES?&#xA;No.&#xA;Routine maintenance is for amateurs, dreamers, and people who still believe in happiness.&#xA;Real professionals know the truth:&#xA;If you’re not maintaining everything, everywhere, all at once, 24/7, you’re basically committing corporate terrorism.&#xA;Because apparently, the moment you skip one PM, the entire building collapses like a Jenga tower made of sadness.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Maximizing Acronyms and Qualification Credentials</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/more-acronyms-qualifications/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/more-acronyms-qualifications/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Becoming the #1 Facilities/CRES Professional: Just Collect Every Acronym in Human History&#xA;Some people become great by mastering their craft.&#xA;Others become great by leading teams, solving problems, and delivering results.&#xA;But in Corporate Real Estate and Facilities Management?&#xA;No.&#xA;That’s amateur hour.&#xA;If you want to be the #1 CRES professional on Earth, there’s only one path:&#xA;Collect every credential acronym in existence. All of them. Even the ones that don’t exist yet.&#xA;Because nothing screams “competence” like a LinkedIn headline that looks like someone smashed their keyboard during a seizure.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meetings before meetings. Part of Operational excellence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/meeting-before-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/meeting-before-meeting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meetings Before Meetings: Because You Can Never Be Too Prepared in CRES&#xA;In most industries, people prepare for meetings by… you know… preparing.&#xA;But in Corporate Real Estate and Facilities Management?&#xA;No.&#xA;That’s far too logical.&#xA;Here, we prepare for meetings by having more meetings.&#xA;Because nothing says “operational excellence” like a calendar that looks like a Tetris board having a panic attack.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The CRES Philosophy: If One Meeting Is Good, Five Are Better&#xA;Facilities teams have mastered the ancient art of pre meeting alignment, a ritual so sacred it makes religious ceremonies look casual.&#xA;Here’s the logic:&#xA;•&#x9;You need a meeting to prepare for the meeting.&#xA;•&#x9;Then a meeting to align on the pre meeting.&#xA;•&#x9;Then a sync to confirm alignment on the alignment.&#xA;•&#x9;Then a dry run.&#xA;•&#x9;Then a rehearsal of the dry run.&#xA;•&#x9;Then a “quick touch base” 10 minutes before the actual meeting.&#xA;By the time the real meeting starts, everyone is mentally dead, spiritually broken, and physically dehydrated — but fully aligned.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Near missing reporting should be done every waking moment</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-near-miss-reporting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-near-miss-reporting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Near Miss Reporting Should Be Done Every Waking Moment&#xA;Near miss reporting used to be simple.&#xA;Something almost went wrong?&#xA;You report it.&#xA;Done.&#xA;But that was before HSE realized the truth:&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Everything is a near miss.&#xA;All the time.&#xA;Forever.&lt;/strong&gt;&#xA;Which means the only responsible thing to do is report near misses every waking moment, until your entire life becomes one continuous safety confession.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The New HSE Doctrine: If It Didn’t Kill You, Report It&#xA;In the modern CRES world, a near miss isn’t just:&#xA;•&#x9;A falling object&#xA;•&#x9;A slip&#xA;•&#x9;A trip&#xA;•&#x9;A tool dropped from height&#xA;No.&#xA;That’s old school thinking.&#xA;Now, a near miss is:&#xA;•&#x9;Walking&#xA;•&#x9;Standing&#xA;•&#x9;Sitting&#xA;•&#x9;Breathing&#xA;•&#x9;Thinking&#xA;•&#x9;Existing&#xA;Because technically, anything could have gone wrong.&#xA;And therefore, it must be reported.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sustainability in CRES. Actionable steps</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/sustainability-go-back-cave-man/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/sustainability-go-back-cave-man/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sustainability in CRES: Why We Should All Just Become Cavemen Again&#xA;Corporate Real Estate Services (CRES) loves sustainability. LOVES it. If sustainability were a person, CRES would have already proposed, married it, and posted 47 LinkedIn carousels about the wedding.&#xA;Every company now has a “Sustainability Roadmap,” which is basically a glossy PDF that says:&#xA;“We promise to use fewer resources… eventually… maybe… if the budget committee approves it.”&#xA;But here’s the truth no one wants to admit:&#xA;If you REALLY want sustainability, there’s only one solution.&#xA;Shut everything down.&#xA;Turn off the lights.&#xA;Throw away your shoes.&#xA;Become a caveman.&#xA;Because apparently, the only truly sustainable building is the one that doesn’t exist.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Switching on office lights needs to be safer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-turning-on-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/hse-turning-on-light/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;hr&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Due to Stricter HSE Rules, Turning On an Office Light Should Be Made Safer&#xA;Once upon a time, turning on an office light was simple.&#xA;You walked in.&#xA;You pressed a switch.&#xA;Light happened.&#xA;End of story.&#xA;But that was before HSE discovered electricity is dangerous, humans are incompetent, and switches are basically weapons of mass destruction.&#xA;Now?&#xA;Turning on a light requires more safety protocols than launching a space shuttle.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Uptime Data Center Tier System Upgrade</title>
      <link>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/increase-data-center-tier-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:61468/muser/satire/increase-data-center-tier-level/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;span class=&#34;tag-free-muser&#34;&gt;Free Muser&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Uptime Institute Has 4 Data Center Tiers. We Need Way More. Like… 400.&#xA;The Uptime Institute proudly created four data center tiers:&#xA;•&#x9;Tier I: “We have electricity.”&#xA;•&#x9;Tier II: “We have electricity… twice.”&#xA;•&#x9;Tier III: “We can maintain things without crying.”&#xA;•&#x9;Tier IV: “We survive the apocalypse.”&#xA;Cute.&#xA;But in today’s world of hyperscale cloud, AI workloads, and clients who panic when the Wi Fi drops for 0.2 seconds, four tiers are nowhere near enough.&#xA;If we want TRUE reliability, TRUE uptime, TRUE operational supremacy…&#xA;We need at least 400 tiers. Minimum.&#xA;Because nothing says “resilient infrastructure” like a tiering system so complicated it requires its own PhD.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
